THE COUNTER-SECRET POLICE COVER OPERATION
Now, who can answer this question?
Miss Anya Forger.
Three-thirds!
Ah. That is quite wrong.
So, how are things going, Twilight?
How is your daughter doing
with her academics?
HQ was estimating that she'd be able to
receive eight Stella in about four months.
Four...
Not a problem.
I see... that your ability
to lie has diminished.
I'm confident she'll be able to get eight
Tonitrus Bolts in two months, though.
No matter.
By the way...
Our informant within city hall
was compromised this morning.
The enemy is stepping up their game.
Be on your guard, Twilight.
I shouldn't have to say this
about being in the city,
but be it at Eden College or elsewhere,
you never know where eyes
will be watching you.
This country's counter-intelligence
agency is quite tough.
H-How can I help you gentlemen?
We're with the State Security Service.
You're Jim Hayward, are you not?
We're taking you in on
suspicion of being a spy.
A s-spy?! What are you talking about?
Hey... wait!
Stop that! Unhand me at onc—
We'll hear what you have
to say back at the office.
That's totally what happened
this morning! I was so scared!
The guy they took from finance
was apparently leaking
documents from this office.
Oh, he must be a bad person.
Mornin'.
Oh, mornin'!
Good morning, Camilla.
Oh, by the way, Yor, my boyfriend
told me about your marriage.
You haven't even told your
younger brother yet?
Oh, you're right! I'd completely forgotten!
Uh, you forgot? For a whole year?
Wh-What shall I do?
He said he'll be calling you here later.
That's right.
I haven't given him the
number for my new place yet.
I was so relieved our marriage went through
that I blanked on everything else!
Say... is your younger brother a hottie?
Aw, he's a total cutie!
Yes. Yuri is quite adorable.
He would always call me "Sis"
and refused to leave my side.
The State Security Service
Yikes, so he's obsessed with his sister. Pass.
If your brother looks up to you so much,
isn't it kinda mean to forget to tell him that?
Let's start one more time
from the beginning.
How many and what kind of files
did you take from city hall?
Who did you sell them to?
What do they look like?
What is their contact information?
When, where, and how many
times did you meet with them?
Please let me go home.
The State Security Service.
An organization whose goal is to maintain
the peace within their nation.
Since we're both so good at talking,
let's continue, Mr. Hayward.
Its main duties include spy hunting
and keeping an eye on the citizens.
What do you say?
To complete their missions,
they frequently use violence,
wiretapping, intimidation, and torture.
The citizens called them the
"secret police," and they are feared.
Great work, First Lieutenant. The boss
asked me to take over the questioning.
All right. I'll leave the rest to you,
Second Lieutenant Briar.
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
Yuri Briar, age twenty.
He is a member of the secret police.
Why did the boss bring
such a softie into our team?
I admit that he's good,
but frankly, he's just a kid.
Some elite from the Ministry of Foreign
Affairs who quickly rose up the ranks.
When I talked to the boss...
Huh? Well, isn't Yuri adorable?
He's like some cute little puppy.
And that was all.
I-I see...
Well, our organization needs
a kid like him sometimes.
Not to mention, he knows how to do the job,
and he can be quite indiscriminate.
Hello, Mr. Hayward!
You won't get anything out of m—
My older sister actually works
at city hall just like you do!
Huh?
Maybe you know her. She's pretty
and kind, and I'm super proud of her!
I'm actually going to celebrate
her marriage today.
I haven't seen her in forever,
so I'm really excited!
So, yeah. I'd like to get this over
with quickly so I can go home.
Why don't you just spit it all out already?
I-I don't know anything!
Here are photos of your deals.
This is you, isn't it, Mr. Hayward?
Second Lieutenant, you—
How long were you holding on to
important evidence like this?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot to submit them.
You'd be much better off if you were honest.
So, I was just giving them the
papers in exchange for cash.
All I know about him is that he's from
the West. I don't even know his name.
Was there anything awkward about
this man's looks or speech?
Perhaps he didn't act his age?
No, nothing like that.
I see. In that case...
Does the name "Twilight"
sound familiar to you?
Who?
He's a spy from the West.
Apparently, a master of disguise.
He is the villain who is trying
to make this world fall into chaos.
You could call him my natural enemy.
I-If I helped you catch him,
could we just forget about all this?
Do you know something?
Er, no, but let me remember...
If you feed me false information, you'll be
committing another crime, so do be careful.
I just wanted extra money so I could fool
around with girls! I didn't mean any harm.
You have a wife, don't you?
You're a man, too! You must understand!
I was just selling some documents.
I'm no political criminal.
Let me off the hook! Please!
Mr. Hayward, you see...
I haven't told my sister that I work
for the State Security Service.
It's a particularly dangerous job,
so it'd just worry her.
And above all, I don't want her
to know how much dirty work I do.
Mr. Hayward, what you've done is treason.
Perhaps they were nothing more
than pieces of paper to you,
but they may very well put many
of our citizens in danger.
Do you understand?!
Unlike you, I love my family... my sister.
I will do anything to protect this
country where my sister lives.
And I do mean anything.
I don't care how much you torture me!
I will never... sell out my friends!
Curse you and your resilience, Bondman!
If only she could concentrate
on her studies like this.
I only have two bullets left.
How many bullets can Bondman's pistol hold?
Hm? I'm pretty sure it was eight.
So that's two-eighths!
Yes! You're right!
He has two-eighths of his bullets left!
How do you even know those words?
So the cartoon makes things
easier for her to understand?
Th-Th-Th-Th-There's trouble, Loid!
Welcome home, Yor.
He has two-eighths of his bullets left!
Yuri... I mean, my younger brother
is coming here today!
Today?!
So, yes...
He insists on coming over
and congratulating us.
What shall we do? He won't find out
that this marriage is fake, will he?
Don't worry.
I've prepared lovey-dovey couple
accessories for just this sort of occasion.
Papa and Mama are flirting.
We are not!
Mama's little brother still isn't here?
You mean your uncle.
Unkie...
It's late. You should go to bed.
Anya will greet Unkie, too...
It appears as though he's
still stuck at work.
I got a little worked up, and now I'm late.
Ah, but...
I'll finally be able to see Sis!
It's been so long! La, la!
Hurgh!
I can feel the ribs that my
sister broke before tingling.
I'm remembering her loving embrace,
and now my whole body is tingling!
But why in the world did my sister wait
a whole year to tell me she was married?
Could he be some foul villain that
she's afraid of introducing to me?!
I will eliminate every threat within
this country where my sister lives.
That includes her husband, too.
Loid Forger...
If he's some shithead who's threatening my
sister, I'll throw him in a cell immediately.
No, calm down. She mustn't
find out about my job.
In order to protect my
job and my happiness,
I must make sure she never
finds out about this!
Yuri Briar...
The Forgers' only blood relative.
It's easy to slip up around someone you're
emotionally close to. We must be careful.
I cannot lose this family that
I've worked so hard to create.
Everyone has a side they
don't show anyone else.
To their friends, their significant others,
or even their families.
Hello! It's nice to meet you!
I'm Yor's younger brother, Yuri!
They hide what they're truly feeling
through fake smiles or bravado,
and keep their true identities secret.
Welcome.
That is how the world keeps up
the appearance of its temporary peace.
Foreign Minister Windsor met with Westalis's
Foreign Minister Brantz for six days of talks,
with the goal of normalizing diplomatic
relations between the two countries.
I'm going to find out...
if this man is going to
harm our family or not!
if this man is worthy of my sister or not!
No, of course he's not worthy.
Oh, let me take your coat
and the things you're carrying.
Oh, no, there's no need.
Thank you for offering.
I can prepare something simple
for us to eat pretty quickly.
The two of you can go ahead and relax.
Oh, don't mind me.
I would never eat something you've made.
Oh, you look so scary, Yuri.
You must be nervous.
I-I'm not...
Crap. My animosity must've been showing.
Please, make yourself at home.
I could still be worked up from
that interrogation earlier.
I need to play the part of the studious
civil servant in front of my sister!
I need to play the part of the
lovely wife in front of Yuri!
I could never tell him that I got
married so I could continue killing!
Thank you for the flowers, Yuri.
Sure... But, Sis...
I haven't accepted your marriage yet.
Why did you keep this a secret for a year?
How am I supposed to accept
it if you don't explain?
A reasonable question.
Now, then...
About your brother... Why don't we just
go ahead and tell him everything?
The fact that single women are
seen as highly suspicious
is a very serious issue in our times.
I'm sure your brother will understand.
W-We can't!
My brother can be very, er, sensitive.
If he found out that I... I got married
to someone I wasn't in love with,
he would probably lose his composure.
Then we could end up troubling you, Loid...
And I don't want my brother to have to
worry about me over something like this.
Oh, b-but don't worry! I have the
perfect excuse to give him!
I know more about Yuri than
anyone else, so leave this to me!
I'm counting on you, Yor.
Well, Sis? Why didn't you tell me?
W-Well...
B-Because I completely forgot!
Huh? Okay, uh, I...
It completely slipped my mind!
Actually, when I called you the other day,
you told me that you had a partner.
You could've at least told me then!
W-Well...
I forgot that I had forgotten to
tell you about my marriage!
Well, if you say so,
it must be true! Sorry, Sis.
He accepted that?!
When it concerns his sister, this man's
sense of logic goes out the window.
Jeez, Sis! You're such a scatterbrain!
Is this normal for the Briars?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Tch. How dare you interrupt
the fun Sis and I were having?
No... If I keep up this nasty attitude,
Sis might end up hating me.
I need to at least fake—
Isn't Loid's cooking just so delicious?
Hmph! Don't think your cooking is
enough to win me over, you villain!
Oh, right. I actually
brought over some wine.
Please, help yourselves.
How considerate of you.
I'll get you drunk and expose you
for the filthy villain you are!
None for you tonight, Yor.
I know.
Unfortunately.
So where did you two meet?
At the boutique on 3rd Street.
It was so surprising for a man I didn't
know to stare at me like that.
Er, well... She was just
so beautiful, you know...
The way you said that...
This subject will probably lead to
a slip-up. I need to change it.
After a few dinners, we realized
we had a lot in common.
When were these dinners? Where?
How many times did you go?
Which restaurants?
How many encounters led to your courtship?
What made you decide to marry her?
Um...
Why do I feel like I'm being
questioned by an officer?
How do the two of you address each other?
Huh? Er, I call her "Yor."
"Yor"?!
Even I hesitate to use her given name!
S-S-S-Sis, you don't happen to call him
"Loi Loi" or "Loidy," do you?
Huh? Um...
Loidy!
God damn it!
I-I just... call him Loid!
When it concerns his sister, this man's
sense of logic... Well, you know the rest.
Are you all right?
Here, have some water.
What could my sister possibly
like about this guy?!
Just because he can cook a little,
and he's handsome, and tall,
and considerate, and a
doctor, that's just...
That's just...
God damn it!
Yuri, calm down.
I guess neither Briar
holds their liquor well.
By the way, Yuri, I hear you're a diplomat.
Divert, divert...
That's quite the line of work.
Yor loves to brag about you all the time.
Dominic told me the other day that you
went all the way to Hugaria recently.
Huh? Yeah. I mean, it's just work.
But yes. It was a beautiful city.
I wish I could've shown you, Sis.
There were a lot of cafés, too.
There was even an old one that
an empress used to frequent...
You mean in the capital city Obda, right?
There are several delicious
restaurants there.
I went there when I was a medical student.
Oh, really?
I went to Kalpatia often.
The old man who owns it makes a superb stew.
I had that, too! Ah...
So this wine is also from
Hugaria. It's excellent.
This is...
Oh, that...
"I bought it from a shop on Hedger Street."
I found it at a little
shop on Hedger Street.
It must've been pricey.
It's 200 dalc.
Oh, no. It was just around 200 dalc.
I knew it.
That's plenty fancy. Thank you very much.
This conversation...
It's right out of the Ostanian Intelligence
Agency's manual for the art of deception.
It's a conversation template used to fabricate
a story about going to another country.
Meaning this whole story's been a lie.
Besides, the owner of Kalpatia
now has his son running the shop.
And this wine actually costs 300 dalc
now due to a poor harvest.
You may be able to fool an amateur,
but it won't work on me,
Yuri Briar!
I had my reservations as soon as I heard you
worked for the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
That line of work has commonly
been an entryway to espionage.
I had Franky do some digging,
and there are records showing he worked
in that department up until a year ago.
He must've been scouted by the intelligence
agency right before or after that.
Putting all the pieces together,
this man works for the domestic
counter-intelligence agency
that is WISE's mortal enemy...
the secret police!
That said, though it may be dangerous,
as long as he doesn't find
out who I really am,
maintaining this relationship
isn't a bad idea.
If I play my cards right, he could
be a powerful source of information
regarding my enemies.
I'll get you something in return next time.
Isn't it wonderful that you have such
a lovely older brother now, Yuri?
He appears to be concealing
his identity from Yor, too.
He may be easier to
manipulate than I thought.
Yuri?
I told you I wouldn't accept him, Sis!
I'm never going to call him my brother!
You're being rude, Yuri.
Yeah, you're right.
I went out into the world,
made a name for myself,
and I can even buy expensive booze now!
But that's all because of my sister!
Our parents were gone, and we were poor,
so we couldn't even get everything
I'd need for studying.
But...
Sis sure is late. She's still
at her part-time job?
I'm home, Yuri!
Uh, Sis?!
What happened?! You're covered in blood!
What kind of work were you doing?!
Huh? Oh, I'm totally fine.
This isn't my blood, so...
More importantly, look, Yuri!
Ta-da! It's the encyclopedia
set you wanted!
I got paid a lot this time,
so I went ahead and bought it!
Sis...
Ta-da! Here are those snacks
you wanted, Yuri!
Sis would always work
herself to death for me!
You don't have to work anymore, Sis!
So I made up my mind... that I was
going to become a proper adult,
and be a man who could protect my sister.
I'm going to be the one who protects
my one and only family member.
Can you even imagine
how it feels for me to have the
most important person in my life
just suddenly taken from me by some
guy who appeared out of thin air?
Yuri...
Sure, I wanted you to get married
someday and find true happiness.
But that guy has to be someone who
could protect you even better than me!
Are you saying you're up to that task,
Loidy?!
Lo—
I just want to put my
brother's mind at ease.
I...
I love Yor as much as you do, if not more!
My daughter loves Yor very much, too.
Come on... This is just an
act to deceive my brother.
She is already a part of my family.
Even if spears or meteors
rained down from the sky,
I would risk my life to protect her.
This man was a bold liar.
Did he say... meteors?!
I'm confident that I could protect
her from spears, but meteors?!
Is he surprisingly powerful?
But how would he do that?
I-It's easy to claim such things, you liar!
Yeah! You have the face of a liar!
Oh, goodness.
You're so careless sometimes, Yuri!
I have the face of a liar?
Has he seen through me?
Oh, don't worry about it,
Yor. I'll clean it up.
No, that couldn't be.
What? You've been married for a year,
and that's your reaction when your hands touch?
What? Are you actually married?
Wha—
Wh-What are you talking about?
We're so in love.
Y-Yes, exactly.
A likely story... If you're really
married, then prove it to me.
I mean, we have our marriage license...
That's not what I meant!
Kiss right here and now.
Huh?!
Should be easy if you're actually in love.
Er... But if it's in front of someone...
Just once is fine. Then I'll believe you.
If you can't, I'm going to city hall to
have them revoke your marriage license!
This is bad. What should I do?
No, calm down.
I'm Westalis's greatest spy, Twilight.
I've had relations with countless
women on my missions.
If a kiss or two will
keep my mission safe...
If that's all it takes...
What?!
Loid, wait...
I'm just going to do what I always do, Yor.
Come on.
I mean, we need to so we can keep
our fake marriage going, but...
Wha...
What?!
SHOW OFF HOW IN LOVE YOU ARE